A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1990.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1990.
    - HB 1029 (90) Landowner's duty of care, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1030 (90) Virginia Contractor Transaction Recovery Act, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1033 (90) Clinical faculty programs, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1035 (90) Early childhood and daycare services, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1037 (90) Horse racing - Administration of drugs, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1038 (90) Tourism and Travel Services Advisory Board, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1039 (90) Securities registration, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - HB 1041 (90) State Internal Auditor, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1043 (90) Onsite sewage systems, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1044 (90) Fees for adoption services, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1045 (90) Adoption, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1048 (90) Polygraph testing, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1050 (90) Motor vehicle insurers - Assigning points, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1051 (90) Jail Authorities, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1052 (90) Workers' Compensation, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1053 (90) Judicial officers as witnesses, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1058 (90) Volunteer firefighting and rescue organizations - Loans, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 1063 (90) Standards of quality, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1064 (90) Expungement of criminal history information, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1069 (90) Regulation of vendors, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1072 (90) Endangered species, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1075 (90) Cooperative Suppression Program Fund, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1076 (90) Manufactured housing, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1078 (90) Land use taxation, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1080 (90) Juvenile and Domestic Relations District Courts - Dispositional authority, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1081 (90) Private activity bonds, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1084 (90) Disclosure of identity, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1085 (90) Nuisance species, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1087 (90) Mine openings, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1089 (90) Coal and gas road improvement tax for public education, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 1091 (90) Secretary of Public Safety / Secretary of Transportation - Realignment, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1094 (90) Adverse underwriting decisions, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1095 (90) Misquottion of an insurance premium, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1096 (90) Credit Unions, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1101 (90) Real estate tax exemption - Elderly or handicapped, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1102 (90) Taxation on sale of food and beverages, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1103 (90) Unlawful sublease of motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1105 (90) Indebtedness or bond issues, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1106 (90) Special Advisory Commission on Mandated Health Insurance Benefits, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1107 (90) Accident and sickness insurance, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1108 (90) Accident and sickness insurance, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1109 (90) Technical Advisory Panel, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 1110 (90) Virginia Indigent Health Care Trust Fund, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1111 (90) Statewide Area Health Education Center Program, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1112 (90) Moratorium on certificates of public need, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1114 (90) Underground storage tanks, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1116 (90) Icome tax and statement benefits, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1117 (90) Practice of dental hygiene, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 1125 (90) Alcoholic beverages, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1127 (90) Visually impaired children, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1128 (90) Duty of clerks - Recorded writings, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1129 (90) Industrial Development Revenue Bond Act, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1132 (90) Underground Storage Tank Program, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1133 (90) Alcoholic Beverage Control Board - Taxes on licenses, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1134 (90) Ended cases - Disposition of papers, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1135 (90) George A. Jones, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 1136 (90) Legislature - Confirmation of appointments, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bills, 1990.
    - SB 1 (90) Fire supression systems, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 3 (90) Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel Commission, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 4 (90) Toll facilities, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 5 (90) Property tax exemption - Red Fez Club, Inc., 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 6 (90) Property tax exemption - Waterman's Museum, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 7 (90) School board salaries, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 8 (90) Misnomer of parties, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 9 (90) Property tax exemption - Staunton Fine Arts Association, Inc., 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 10 (90) Property tax exemption - Alternatives for Abused Adults, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - SB 11 (90) Disposition of dogs that kill livestock, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 12 (90) Public Defender Commission, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 13 (90) Termination of health insurance coverage, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 16 (90) Taxes on sale of food and beverages, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 17 (90) Charter - Charlottesville (Historic Buildings), 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 19 (90) Property tax exemption - Virginia Maintain Housing, Inc., 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 20 (90) Milk crates, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 22 (90) Property tax exemption - Gabriel Homes, Inc., 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 23 (90) Tow truck operation, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 24 (90) Towing operations - Liability immunity, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 25 (90) Political subdivisions, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 26 (90) Food donations - Civil liability, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 27 (90) David Vasquez, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 28 (90) Taxable property, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 31 (90) Capital projects - Institutions of higher education, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 41 (90) Tax exemption - Northern Virginia Family Services, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 42 (90) Honorable Jack B. Colter, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 43 (90) Interest on insurance claim proceeds, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 44 (90) Constance C. Ratcliffe, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 45 (90) Charter - Edinburg, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 47 (90) Charter - Alexandria, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 49 (90) Charter - Newport News, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 51 (90) Land development, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 54 (90) Charter - Fredericksburg, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 56 (90) County executive form of government - Restrictions, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 61 (90) Virginia Retail Sales and Use Tax Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 62 (90) Virginia Retail Sales and Use Tax Act - Exemptions, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 64 (90) Tax exemption - Virginia Beach Economical Housing, Inc., 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 66 (90) Virginia Retail Sales and Use Tax Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 68 (90) Removal of unsafe vehicles from service, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 69 (90) Motor vehicle speeds, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 70 (90) Virginia Birth Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 72 (90) Virginia Birth Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 74 (90) Annual Statements of Insurers, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 79 (90) Weapons on school property, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 81 (90) Potomac River Basin Compact, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 82 (90) Delinquent taxes, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 83 (90) Free tuition, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 86 (90) Old Reston Avenue - Virginia Byway, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 88 (90) Analysis of water, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 90 (90) Equitable distribution, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 91 (90) Issuance of bonds, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 92 (90) Parking facilities bonds, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 94 (90) Gas severance tax, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 96 (90) Condominium Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 97 (90) Landowners - Duty of care, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 98 (90) Toll roads - Private corporations, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 100 (90) Virginia Consumer Protection Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 101 (90) Income tax credit - Recycling, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 102 (90) Computer trespass, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 103 (90) Local planning commissions, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 104 (90) Public defender offices, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 105 (90) Office of the Attorney General, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 107 (90) Healing arts remuneration, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 108 (90) Liens on livery stables, garages, marinas, ect., 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 111 (90) Child-care services, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 113 (90) Governor George C. Peery Highway, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 114 (90) Watercraft sales and use tax, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 115 (90) Workers' Compensation - Self-insurers, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 116 (90) Life insurance policies, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 117 (90) Local tax returns, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 120 (90) District Court judges, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 121 (90) Circuit Court judges, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 122 (90) Circuit Court judges, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 125 (90) Juveniles tried as adults - Subsequent offenders, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 126 (90) Workers' Compensation Uninsured Employers Fund, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 129 (90) Facilities for treating mentally ill, retarded and drug addiction, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 130 (90) DNA analysis, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 132 (90) Motor vehicle licenses, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 133 (90) Blue Star Memorial Highway and Coleman's Bridge (Orange County), 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 134 (90) Bingo games, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 135 (90) Mammograms, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 136 (90) Recylcing, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 138 (90) Motor vehicle dealers - License tax, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 139 (90) Optometry, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 140 (90) Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SB 141 (90) Abuse and neglect of children, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 142 (90) Heath maintenance organizations, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 143 (90) Income producing real property, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 144 (90) Child-care services and facilities, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 146 (90) Local ordinances, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 147 (90) Juvenile transportation from detention homes, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 148 (90) Workers' Compensation - Coal worker's pneumoconiosis, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 149 (90) ABC laws and farm wineries, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 152 (90) Livery liens - defrauding, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 153 (90) Nuisances - Local abatement or removal, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 155 (90) Literary Fund, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 156 (90) Concealed weapons, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 159 (90) Bingo games, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - SB 162 (90) Ports and harbours, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 163 (90) County administrators, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 165 (90) County boards of supervisors, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 166 (90) Farmers' exemption for civil liability, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 168 (90) Improvement of abandoned or neglected graveyards, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 170 (90) Transportation improvement districts, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SB 176 (90) Rockfish River - Scenic River designation, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 177 (90) Damaging public buildings, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 179 (90) Rappahannock River - Scenic River designation, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 182 (90) Virginia Resources Authority, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 183 (90) Restoration of habitat, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 184 (90) Transfer hearings in juvenile court, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 185 (90) Children taken into custody, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 186 (90) Incarceration in local correctional facilities, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 187 (90) Classification of tangible personal property, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 189 (90) Secrecy of tax information, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 190 (90) Virginia Waste Management Act, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SB 191 (90) State Water Control Act, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 192 (90) Soybean assessments, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 193 (90) Virginia Solid and Hazardous Waste Contingency Fund, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 194 (90) Youth Services - Board and Dept., 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 199 (90) Excess Cost Recovery Program, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 203 (90) Claims made - Liability insurance policies, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 204 (90) In-state tuition charges, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 205 (90) Prescription in excell of recommended doses, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 208 (90) Day-care programs outside of school hours, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 209 (90) Public Defender Commission, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 211 (90) Protection of agricultural animals from coyotes, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 215 (90) Motor vehicle licenses, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 217 (90) Pawnbrokers, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 218 (90) Abuse, neglect and exploitation of adults, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 220 (90) Water and sewer - Connections and liens, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SB 222 (90) Water quality test results, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 223 (90) Toll facilities, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 224 (90) Virginia Scenic River System, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 226 (90) Parole, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 229 (90) Planning, subdivision of land, and zoning definitions, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 230 (90) Motor vehicles - Towing and immobilization, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 234 (90) Uniform Foreign Country Money - Judgments Recognition Act, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 237 (90) Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Appeals of eligibility determinations, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - SB 241 (90) Special education, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 242 (90) Special education, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 243 (90) Unemployment Trust Fund, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 246 (90) Educational institutions - Bonds, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 247 (90) Institutions of higher learning - Leases, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 249 (90) Income tax credits, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 250 (90) Individual income tax and state retirement benefits, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 252 (90) Voluntary apprenticeship, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 254 (90) Commissioner of Social Services, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 258 (90) Criminal Justice Services, Board, Committee on Training and Advisory Committee on Juvenile Justice, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - SB 263 (90) Controlled substances, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 265 (90) Medical records - Copies, charges, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 270 (90) Rights of way, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 271 (90) Parentage proceedings, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 274 (90) County property, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 275 (90) Permits for structures and zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 276 (90) Motor fuel tax - Boats and ships, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 277 (90) Council on the Environment - Non-tidal wetlands, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 278 (90) Special elections, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 279 (90) Residential facilities for the disabled - Zoning, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - SB 281 (90) Media in the courtroom, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 287 (90) Recylcing, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 288 (90) Virginia Public Procurement Act, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 289 (90) Tangible personal property, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 297 (90) Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Commission, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 298 (90) Visually handicapped - Operation of businesses, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 301 (90) Violations of zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 302 (90) Prescription of drugs, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 303 (90) Cosmetology laws, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 306 (90) Smoke detectors, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 310 (90) Speed check of vehicles, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - SB 311 (90) Central Criminal Record Exchange, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 313 (90) Tangible personal property, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 317 (90) Retail sales tax, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 318 (90) Virginia Transportation Contract Revenue Bonds, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 319 (90) Virginia Port Authority, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 320 (90) Judges - Standards of conduct, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 321 (90) Central Criminal Records Exchange, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 322 (90) Special land use assessments, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 323 (90) Virginia Public Building Authority Act, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 328 (90) Deferral of real estate taxes, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 329 (90) Payment dates for local taxes, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - SB 332 (90) Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 333 (90) Check cashing, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 335 (90) Solicitation of charitable donations, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 336 (90) Clinical evaluation of sex offenders, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 337 (90) Community Prevention Initiative Grant Program, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 338 (90) Public benefits delivery systems, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 339 (90) Statewide Council on Infant Mortality, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - SB 341 (90) Parking spaces reserved for the handicapped, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 342 (90) Virginia Public Building Authority Act, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 343 (90) Boiler and pressure vessel safety, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 346 (90) Certificates evidencing shares and form of bonds, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 347 (90) Stock corporations, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 348 (90) Shareholder rights to dissent, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 349 (90) Corporation mergers, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 350 (90) Noise ordinances - Augusta County, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 351 (90) Estate tax, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 353 (90) Youthful Offender Program, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 354 (90) Dates for filing tax returns and paying real estate tax, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 356 (90) Virginia Small Business Financing Act, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 357 (90) Jail and jail farm boards, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 358 (90) Virginia Racing Commission, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - SB 367 (90) School board reimbursement - Pre-school special education programs, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 369 (90) Smoke detectors, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 375 (90) Fire bombs and explosive devices - Penalties, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 377 (90) Licensure of facilities and institutions, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 378 (90) Distribution of drugs on school property, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 379 (90) Written contracts for teachers, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 380 (90) Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Board, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 381 (90) Coalbed methane gas, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 382 (90) Gas and oil resources, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 383 (90) Applications for certificates to discharge sewage waste, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 385 (90) State Police regulations, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 388 (90) Juvenile Courts, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - SB 390 (90) Detention of juveniles, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 393 (90) Juvenile court records, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 394 (90) Industrial development authorities, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 395 (90) Virginia Equine Center Foundation, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 397 (90) Parole, Probation, Work Release, Diversion Program, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 398 (90) Firearms, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 399 (90) Property tax returns, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 401 (90) Public retirement systems, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 404 (90) General District Courts, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 408 (90) Alcoholic Beverage Control Board - Licenses, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 409 (90) Overpayments for medical assistance services, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 410 (90) Alcoholic Beverage Control - Licenses, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - SB 415 (90) Historical societies, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 416 (90) Subdivision ordinances, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 417 (90) Boot Camp Incarceration Program, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 418 (90) Sale of real estate for delinquent taxes, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 419 (90) Treasury Board - Bonds, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 422 (90) Committees and trustees, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 425 (90) State Police reports, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 429 (90) Zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 439 (90) Virginia Racing Commission, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - SB 445 (90) Computation of Virginia taxable income, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 446 (90) Adding candidate names to ballots, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 447 (90) Recyling report ordinances, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 448 (90) Industrial Loan Association, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 449 (90) Forest products tax, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 451 (90) Regional Health Plan, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 452 (90) Curb ramps, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 453 (90) Abandoned motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 454 (90) Emergency Medical Services, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 455 (90) Humane societies, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 456 (90) Voter registation rolls - Purging, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 457 (90) Oil and gas drilling in Atlantic Ocean, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 458 (90) Health spas, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 459 (90) Nursing facility services, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - SB 460 (90) Statewide Emergency Medical Services Plan, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 462 (90) School Health Advisory Boards, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 463 (90) Licensure to practice medicine, osteopathy, chiropractic and podiatry, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 465 (90) Discharge into state waters, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 467 (90) Opticians and eye glasses duplication, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 470 (90) Vacation of plat after sale of lot, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 471 (90) State Corporation Commission - Jurisdiction over health care services, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 476 (90) Capital cases - Sentencing procedures, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)